UTU New York State Legislative Director Files 5711
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Correspondence. 1969-1971. (Box 14)
  - Endorsements, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - J.H. Shepherd, General Secretary and Treasurer of the United Transportation Union, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Department of Transportation (Federal and State), 1971 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Trainmen's Political Education League, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - A.H. Chesser National Legislative Director, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - First United Transportation Union Convention, Miami Beach, Florida, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - General Secretary and Treasurer Monthly Reports, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Charles Luna, President of the United Transportation Union, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - J.H. Shepherd, General Secretary and Treasurer, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - National Conference State Legislative Representative, 1962-1967 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Railpax, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    Package
  - Railpax Law Enacted, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Governor, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Scholarship Fund, United Transportation Union, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Office Re-Location, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - State Hearings, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Time Slips, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Trainmen's Political Education League: Organizational File, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - United Transportation Union: News, State Legislative Board, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Trainmen's Political Education League: Monthly Recap Sheets, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Trainmen's Political Education League, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Statements of Expense, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - United Transportation Union (Cleveland): Articles, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - United Transportation Union (Cleveland): Topics, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Trainmen's Political Education League: Monthly Recapitulation Sheets, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 35)
- Correspondence. 1972-1973. (Box 15)
  - Department of Transportation: Calendar of Hearings, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), New York State: Bulletins, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - F.B. Boardman, Assistant Director, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Al H. Chesser, President, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Crew Consists, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Department of Transportation (Federal and State), 1972 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Department of State: J.P. Lomenzo, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - General Secretary and Treasurer: Monthly Reports, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Legislative Party: Mario's, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Legislative Directory Changes, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Legislative Representative, 1968-1972 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - New York State Department of Labor: Newsletter, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Railroad Retirement, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Governor, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Reorganization Meeting, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - United Transportation Union: Scholarship Fund, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - United Transportation Union: Scholarship Fund, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - General Secretary and Treasurer J.H. Shepherd, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - R.J. Snyder, National Legislative Director, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Statement of Expense, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Time Slips, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Statement of Expense: F.B. Boardman, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Executive Committee Meetings, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Trainmen's Political Education League, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Trainmen's Political Education League: Monthly Recap Sheets, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Trainmen's Political Education League: Non-Paying Members, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Trainmen's Political Education League: Organizational File, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Trainmen's Political Education League: Recap by "T," "E", and "C" Locals, 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Background Information, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Assembly 229 (Tills): Spark Arrester, Locomotives, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Assemblyman C. Henderson on New York Bankrupt Railroads, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Miscellaneous Letters, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Washington News, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    April 1973
  - Lehigh Valley Railroad, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission (ICC) Abandonment Hearings, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - News Story of Legislature, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Retired and Veteran Railway Employer Group: Pete McGuire, Lobbyist, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Department of Transportation Calendar of Hearings, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Al H. Chesser, President, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - United Transportation Union: News, State Legislative Board, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - New York State Department of Labor: Newsletter, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), New York State: Bulletins, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), New York State: Convention, Concord Hotel, Kiamesha Lake, New York, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    September 5-7, 1973
  - Department of Transportation (Federal and State), 1973 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Executive Committee: Election, Bus Representative, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Executive Committee: Meetings, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - General Secretary and Treasurer: Monthly Reports, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 48)
- Correspondence. 1973-1974. (Box 16)
  - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), New York State: Constitutional Convention, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Bound.
  - Legalized Numbers: A Plan to Operate a Legal Numbers Game Now, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    Bound. February 1973
  - Statement of Expense, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - G.W. Rogers, Legislative Board Director, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - General Secretary and Treasurer J.H. Shepherd, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - National Legislative Director J.R. Snyder, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Rail Services Act, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Special Expense Allotment, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Time Slips, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Trainmen's Political Education League, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - United Transportation Union: News, State Legislative Board, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Trainmen's Political Education League: Monthly Recap Sheets, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Correspondence. 1975-1976. (Box 17)
  - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), New York State: Convention, Kiamesha Lake, New York, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    October 30-31 and November 1, 1975
  - Public Transportation Operating Assistance: Annual Report, Programs in New York State, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), New York State: Bulletins, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - F.B. Boardman, Assistant Director, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - F.B. Boardman, 1969-1975 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - F.B. Boardman, Assistant Director, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - F.B. Boardman, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - General Secretary and Treasurer Monthly Reports, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Governor Hugh L. Carey, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Al H. Chesser, President, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Victor Condello, New York Railroad Association, 1968-1974 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Department of Transportation: Calendar of Hearings, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Department of Transportation (Federal and State), 1975 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Department of State: Mario Cuomo, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - United Transportation Union: Political Endorsements and Money Sent to Candidates, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Legislative Representatives, 1972-1975 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Legislative Directory Changes, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Kenneth R. Moore, Bus Department Director, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - News from United States Railway Association, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Newspaper Correspondence, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Railroad Retirement, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - G.W. Rogers, State Director, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - United Transportation Union: Scholarship Fund, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - R.T. Schuler, Commissioner, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - General Secretary and Treasurer J.H. Shepherd, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - J.R. Snyder, National Legislative Director, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Special Expense Allotment, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Statement of Expense, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Trainmen's Political Education League, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Time Slips, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Trainmen's Political Education League: Monthly Recap Sheets, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - United Transportation Union: News, State Legislative Board, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Endorsements, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Department of Transportation Calendar of Hearings, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Endorsement and Contribution Letters to Legislators, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Thank You Letters from Legislators, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Al H. Chesser, President, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 40)
- Correspondence. 1976-1977. (Box 18)
  - Closing New York State Locals, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Department of Transportation (Federal and State), 1976 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Election of Vice Chairman, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Election of Daniel P. Moynihan to the United States Senate, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Legislative Directory Changes, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - General Information, 1969-1975 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - General Secretary and Treasurer: Monthly Reports, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Locomotive Engineer, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - G.W. Rogers, State Director, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Penn-Central Company, Incorporated, 1968-1971 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Railroad Retirement, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - United Transportation Union: Scholarship Fund, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - R.T. Schuler, Commissioner: News Release, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - R.T. Schuler, Commissioner, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - General Secretary and Treasurer J.H. Shepherd, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - National Legislative Director J.R. Snyder, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Special Expense Allotment, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Statement of Expense, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Time Slips, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Trainmen's Political Education League: Monthly Recap Sheets, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Trainmen's Political Education League, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - G.W. Rogers: Newsletter, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - United States Railroad Retirement Board: Informational Conference Handbook, 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 26)
- Case Files. Penn Central. (Box 19)
  - William Galloway, Director of the Department of Transportation, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Department of Transportation Rail Accident Report (Box 19, Folder 2)
    Package. No date.
  - Penn-Central Rider Cars - Unsafe (All Locals), 1970 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Use of reflectorized markers on rear of trains in lieu of lighted markers, 1962-1966 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Unsafe Conditions in White Plains, New York, New York Central Railroad, 1963-1968 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Pennsylvania Railroad General Committee: Modifications, Rule 99 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    Found Empty October 7, 2014. No date.
  - Unsafe Conditions at Harmon Yard Refueling Station, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    Includes Photographs
  - Unsafe Operating Practices: New York Central, Frontier Yard, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Operation of Locomotives in the Right Direction on the Norfolk and Western Railroad, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    January 22, 1976
  - Unsafe Conditions: Dewitt and Geddes Station Yards, New York Central Railroad, 1967-1968 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Regarding crews on sides of cars, New York Central Railroad, 1967-1968 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Unsafe Operation Train 980, Harlem Division, New York Central Railroad, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    May 23, 1967
  - Regarding Unsafe Conditions in the Auburn Road Area of New York Central Railroad and Dewitt, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    May 19, 1967
  - Public Service Commission: Correspondence regarding additional charge to shippers for turning car for unloading, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Regarding Trainman's Seat on A.S.16 type Engines Pennsylvania Railroad, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    May 3, 1967
  - Unsafe Conditions, West Yard, Oswego, New York, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    April 26, 1967
  - Regarding unsafe conditions of yard engines, Oak Point and Harlem Division Yards, New Haven Rail, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - New York Central's Track 916 Lack of Flagging Equipment, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    July 3, 1967
  - Unsafe and Unsanitary Conditions, Olean Terminal, Pennsylvania Railroad, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    July 1967
  - Close Clearance, General Abrasives Plant - Niagara Yard, New York Central Railroad, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Alleged Violation of Safety Appliance Act, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    September 6, 1967
  - Regarding Movement of "Tagged Car" by Penn-Central Railroad, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    February 20, 1968
  - Regarding Condition of Bridge W-8, Rochester, New York, Penn-Central Railroad, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    April 1968
  - Unsafe Conditions, YMCA East Syracuse, New York, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Unsafe Conditions, Various Cement Plans, 1968-1973 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Unsafe Conditions on Harlem, Penn-Central, 1968-1971 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Trucks used to Transport Trainmen, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    August 16, 1968
  - Unsafe Working Conditions, Elmira-Canandaigua, New York, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    August 19, 1968
  - Discipline Syracuse Division Train 71, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    June 14, 1968
  - Hunts Point Unsafe Working Conditions (Garcia), 1968 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    July 30, 1968
  - Caboose 477525 Inspection, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    July 1, 1968
  - Caboose Complaints, Watertown, New York, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    June 25, 1968
  - Unsafe Working Conditions, Grand Central Terminal, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    September 9, 1968
  - Caboose Complaints, Safety Air-Valve, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    November 6, 1968
  - Unsafe Working Conditions, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    August 26, 1968
  - Caboose Complaints, Penn-Central, Olean, New York, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 36)
    August 15, 1968
  - Unsafe Conditions, Rochester, New York, Goodman Station Yard, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Checked Baggage, Penn-Central and Delaware and Hudson, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Empire Service, Penn-Central, 1968-1970 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Debris Alongside Tracks, Minoa Yard, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 40)
    November 18, 1968
  - Unsafe Railing A.E. Smith Bridge, Selkirk, New York, Penn-Central, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 41)
    November 27, 1968
  - Unsafe Conditions, Frontier Yard, Buffalo, New York, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 42)
    December 9, 1968
  - Penn-Central Station, Rensellaer, New York, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 43)
    December 30, 1968
  - Massena, New York Taxi Rides unheated, etcetera, Penn-central, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 44)
    January 7, 1969
  - Unsafe Conditions, Seneca Yard, Buffalo, New York, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 45)
    January 23, 1969
  - Unsafe Conditions, Lockport, New York, Penn-Central Railroad, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Penn-Central at Dewitt, Violations of Section 5 of close Clearance, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 47)
    March 18, 1969
  - Penn-Central Guard Rails on Tracks 3 and 4, Bridges C1 and C2, unsafe, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 48)
    April 4, 1969
  - Thirty-Third (33rd) Street Yard New York Central: Unsafe Conditions, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 49)
    March 24, 1969
  - Tracks and Road Beds, Olean New York, Unsafe Conditions, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 50)
    April 25, 1969
  - Unsafe track conditions, etcetera: Rochester, New York, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 51)
    August 13, 1973
  - Penn-Central Goodman Station Yard, Rochester, New York; Oil and Unsafe Conditions, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 52)
    May 7, 1969
- Grand Central Terminal, New York Central and New Haven: Coaches' removal safety devices, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  June 17, 1969
- Selkirk Yard, Penn-Central Railroad: Unsafe and Close Clearance Violations, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  June 19, 1969
- Penn-Central at Syracuse, New York: Unsafe Working Conditions, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  July 17, 1969
- Putnam Junction and white Plains: Unsafe Conditions, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  August 5, 1969
- Klingston, New York, Penn-Central Railroad: Unsafe Conditions, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  July 23, 1969
- Corning, New York Proper: Unsafe Conditions, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  July 24, 1969
- Niagara Junction Railroad and Penn-Central Railroad: Unsafe Conditions, Niagara Falls, New York, 1969-1971 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Lehigh Valley Railroad, Buffalo, New York: Unsafe Conditions, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  September 15, 1969
- Penn-Central Rochester, New York: Subway Unsafe Conditions, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  June 23, 1969
- Penn-Central Selkirk, New York: Vegetation, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  October 21, 1969
- Penn-Central Railroad, Maybrook, New York: Unsafe Conditions, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  October 2, 1969
- Penn-Central Oak Point, New York: Unsafe Conditions, close Clearance, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  November 26, 1969
- Bus Local: Unsafe Bus Conditions, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  January 2, 1970
- Penn-Central, Buffalo, New York: Unsafe Conditions, Close Clearance, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  January 26, 1970
- Penn-Central, Charlotte, New York: Close Clearance and Unsafe Conditions, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  April 5, 1970
- Department of Transportation: Unsafe Condition Entering Frontier Yard in Buffalo, New York off Route 130, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  June 9, 1970
- Penn-Central: Unsafe Conditions, Yard and Caboose, Olean, New York, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  June 29, 1970
- Penn-Central: Unsafe Conditions in Mamaroneck and Mount Vernon, New York, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  October 21, 1970
- Penn-Central, Harlem Division: Unsafe City Road 80, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  November 11, 1970
- Department of Transportation: Snow Removal Forced to Walk Route 57, Fulton, New York, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  February 24, 1970
- Department of Transportation: cabooses without Electric Markers, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  March 9, 1971
- Penn-Central: Unsafe Condition, Hunts Point Yard, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  May 4, 1971
- Penn-Central: Violation of Chapter 693 54-B, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- Penn-Central: Unsafe Conditions in Newburgh Yard, Kingston, New York, etcetera, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- Penn-Central Transit Company, Grand Central Terminal: M Type Equipment, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  September 21, 1971
- Penn-Central, Harlem Division: New Passenger Equipment, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 26)
- Unsafe Conditions, Cabooses - Olean, New York, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  September 1, 1971
- Unsafe Conditions, Potsdam, New York, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  October 19, 1971
- Embargoes on several branches of Penn-Central Transit Company, Incorporated, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  October 25, 1971
- Debris siding of team track, Little Falls, New York, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  December 1971
- Penn-Central: Yonkers Freight yard, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  November 1971
- Unsafe Working Conditions, Kingston, New York, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  November 24, 1971
- Grand Central Terminal and Croton-North Station: Commuter Coaches, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 33)
- Frontier Yard, Buffalo, New York: Unsafe Working Conditions, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 34)
- Little Falls Yard: Debris and Water, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 35)
- Vegetation between Syracuse and Buffalo, New York, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  August 14, 1972
- Penn-Central: Caboose Law Violations, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  October 13, 1972
- Flagging Stations Between Ossining and Ludlow, New York, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  December 6, 1972
- Penn-Central, Charlotte Branch: Flagging, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  January 4, 1973
- Penn-Central: Unsafe Conditions, West 72nd Street Yard Area, New York Central, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  March 2, 1973
- Albany: Port Traveling Switcher, Interchange Yard, Port of Albany, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  April 9, 1973
- Penn-Central: Taxi Cab Discontinuance between Penn Yard and Seneca Yard, Buffalo, New York, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  June 8, 1973
- Penn-Central: Unsafe Working Conditions, Kenmore Yard, Buffalo, New York, Local 1393, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  September 14, 1973
- Penn-Central: Unsafe Conditions; Marlboro, Roseton, Walkill Valley B ranch, Local 899, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 44)
- Penn-Central: Second Belt Travelling Switcher, West Ridge Road Crossing, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  November 27, 1973
- Unsafe Conditions Between CP-3 - CP-123 and Germantown, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  May 8, 1974
- Standees on Passenger Trains between New York Central and Albany, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 47)
- Norfolk and Western: Unsafe Working Conditions, Bison Yard, Buffalo, New York, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  June 25, 1974
- Penn-Central, Rochester and Charlotte, New York: Weeks and Debris, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  July 19, 1974
- Croton Harmon, New York Area: Unsafe Working Conditions, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  September 10, 1974
- Penn-Central: Inspection on Catskill Mountain Branch, Kingston, New York, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  September 23, 1974
- Penn-Central: Unsafe Working Conditions, Hammermill Paper Company, Port Alleghany, Pennsylvania, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 52)
  November 4, 1974
- Penn-Central: Proposed Abandonments and Service, Hojack, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 53)
  November 12, 1974
- Penn-Central: 982 - Unsafe Working Conditions, American Can Company, Fairport, New York. Also, Garlock Packing Company: Barb Wire Fence, Palmyra, New York., 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 54)
  December 10, 1974 and March 28, 1975
- Penn-Central: Yard Area, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 55)
  March 3, 1975
- Unsafe Working Conditions, Buffalo, New York area, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 56)
  April 17, 1975
- Penn-Central: Unsafe Working Conditions in Massena, New York area, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 57)
  May 2, 1975
- Penn-Central: Weed and Debris, Seneca Yard, Lackawanna New York; Ashtabula, Ohio, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 58)
  August 1974
- Penn-Central: Weeds, etcetera in Olean, New York-Buffalo, New York, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 59)
  August 6, 1975
- Penn-Central, Harlem Division: Passenger Equipment Malfunctioning, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 60)
  August 18, 1975
- Penn-Central: Slow Orders Between Mile Posts 375.5 and 372 on Track 2 at Rochester, New York, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 61)
  July 1, 1975
- Unsafe Conditions Existing at 138th Street and Grand Central Terminal, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 62)
  November 26, 1975
- Close Clearance, Flanagan Furniture, Maple Street, Rochester, New York, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 63)
  September 29, 1975
- Close Clearance, Agway Soil Division, Batavia, New York, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 64)
  November 24, 1975
- Penn-Central: Bridge Inspection (Genesee River Bridge), Rochester, New York, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 65)
  January 13, 1976
- Penn-Central Yards, Dunkirk, New York, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 66)
- Unsafe Working Conditions, Selkirk, New York Fueling Station, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 67)
  January 21, 1976
- Lighting, Engine House, Kingston, New York, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 68)
  October 29, 1976
- Unsafe Working Conditions, Oak Street, Rochester, New York, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 69)